<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="release_note_3_6"><![CDATA[
Version 3.6<br>
<br>
New:<br>
- Redesign of the history screen. The buttons for deleting a record and editing a description are brought to the foreground, so you no longer need to swipe.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="release_note_3_5"><![CDATA[
Version 3.5.0<br>
<br>
New:<br>
- Added arrows to move the cursor to the right/left in the currency converter and in the number system converter;<br>
- When formatting, a space is added after the semicolon (;).<br>
Corrections:<br>
- Accelerated data loading for the currency converter.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="release_note_3_2"><![CDATA[
Version 3.2.0<br>
<br>
New:<br>
- Now you can use the arrows near the fields to quickly scroll to the beginning or end.<br>
- Some functions from the sidebar have been combined under one button (they are indicated by a dot in the lower right corner). To access them, you need a long press.<br>
Corrections:<br>
- Fixed a problem with function bases (for example, earlier the expression "log0.75(0.5)" was interpreted as "decimal logarithm 0.75 multiplied by 0.5" ("log0.75×(0.5)"), and should be "logarithm 0.5 based on 0.75")
    ]]></string>

    <string name="release_note_3_0"><![CDATA[
Version 3.0<br>
<br>
New:<br>
- Added currency converter.<br>
- New design of number generator and number system converter.<br>
- Added new bugs.<br>
Corrections:<br>
- Fixed old bugs.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="release_note_2_8"><![CDATA[
Version 2.8.0<br>
<br>
<b>New:</b><br>
- Now trigonometric functions accept arguments in radians by default.<br>
Added the degree (&deg;) and gradian (&#7586;) operators to calculate the value from the angle in degrees or gradians.<br>
They can also be used to convert to radians (for example, 30&deg; = 0.526)<br>
- The design of the settings has been updated<br>
<b>Corrections:</b><br>
- Fixed a bug where the result of the premise was added to the history
    ]]></string>

    <string name="release_note_2_7"><![CDATA[
Version 2.7.0<br>
<br>
<b>New:<b><br>
- Updated password generator. Now it is customizable and generates more reliable passwords;<br>
- Added the "Save history" setting.<br>
<br>
<b>Other:</b><br>
- Bug fixes
    ]]></string>

    <string name="release_note_2_6"><![CDATA[
Version 2.6.0<br>
<br>
<b>New:</b><br>
- The panel with functions and constants has been moved to the first panel in the scrollable list<br>
- Added cotangent, arcotangent, arcsine, arccosine, arctangent<br>
- Added gcd and lcm<br>
- Added the base of the root (√4(16) will show 2 means the square root of 16 base 4, but √4 or √(4) means the square root of 4 base 2) <br>
- Added lists (several independent expressions separated by semicolons, on which operations can be performed)<br>
You can read more about the lists at this <a href=\'https://github.com/MaxSavTeam/calculator-core/releases/tag/2.0.0\'>link</a><br>
<br>
<b>Corrections:</b><br>
- Improved accuracy of calculations<br>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="release_note_2_4"><![CDATA[
Version 2.4.0<br>
<br>
Added support for landscape orientation and multi-window mode.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="release_note_2_3"><![CDATA[Version 2.3.0. What\'s new?<br><br>Now you can choose where to save the backup file of the application settings, as well as choose from which file to restore.<br><br>Fixed system navigation coloring depending on the app theme.]]></string>

    <string name="release_note_2_1"><![CDATA[Version 2.1.0. What\'s new?<br><br>Now you can enter numbers and other operations anywhere in the example.<br>Just put the cursor there.<br><br>Now the decimal and integer separator and the digit group separator are localized for each language.]]></string>

    <string name="release_note_2_0"><![CDATA[We are introducing version 2.0.<br>It has a lot of changes both in the user interface and internal functional improvements.<br><br>From the interface changes:<br>- Mathematical operations (which were on the numbers) are moved to a separate panel, which can be opened by swiping to the left.<br>- Added a beautiful ripple when you click on the numbers and operations buttons.<br>- New notation of the Euler number.<br><br>From functional changes:<br>- Added the Fi number (1.618)<br>- Added an arbitrary base of the logarithm. For example, the expression "log2(64)" is equivalent to "logarithm 64 on base 2", and the expression "log 20" is equivalent to "logarithm 20 on base 10".<br>- Removed the geometric mean function due to uselessness.<br><br>The method of parsing and counting the expression has also been changed, which is more optimal from the point of view of work and from the point of view of maintenance by the developer.]]></string>

</resources>